Guide to the William Goyen Papers, 1937-1978 MS 360
Woodson Research Center, Rice University, Houston, Texas
- Series I: Correspondence
  - Correspondence from Goyen to his family, 1940-1943; (161 items)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, April 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, May 7, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, May 11, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, May 18, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, May 22, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, May 28, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, June 4, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, June 7, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, June 13, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, June 20, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, June 27, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - invitation to attend commissioning USS Casablanca, June 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - parents from (aboard USS Casablanca), July 11, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), July 14, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - family from (aboard USS Casablanca), July 20, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), July 24, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), July 31, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), August 5, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - parents from (aboard USS Casablanca), Aug. 14, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - parents from (aboard USS Casablanca), Aug. 24, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), Aug. 28, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - father from (aboard USS Casablanca), Aug. 29, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from (aboard USS Casablanca), Aug. 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 4, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 6, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Sept. 8, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 13, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
      - 1 p. from USS C's newspaper, Flat Topics
        w/enclosure
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 15, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 17, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 19, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 20, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 27, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Sept. 30, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 4-5, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 25, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 28, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 1, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 6, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 10, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 15, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 20, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 26, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Dec. 3, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 7, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - M.H. Graham to Mrs. C.P. Goyen, Tacoma, Washington, Dec. 7, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Dec. 11, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 13, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - Telegram to mother from Tacoma, Washington, Dec. 25, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Dec. 27, 1943 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Goyen letters to family, 1944-45, 1948-49; 188 items
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 7, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Jan. 16, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 16, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 21, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Jan. 22, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - from, Jan. 9, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 29, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - parents (Valentine's Day card) USS C, Feb. 8, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - Em from USS Casablanca, Feb. 8, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 17, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 27, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, March 5, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 11, 1944
    - father from USS Casablanca, Mar. 11, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 18, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 22, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 4, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 11, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 24, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 27, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 5, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - father from USS Casablanca, May 10, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 16, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, May 26, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 1)
    - parents from Bremerton, Washington, June 10, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from Bremerton, Washington, June 13, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from Bremerton, Washington, June 20, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from Bremerton, Washington, June 27, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from Bremerton, Washington, July 2, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, July 9, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, July 12, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - mother from Hollywood, California, Aug. 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 3, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Aug. 4, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 7, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 13, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 18, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 22, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Aug. 26, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 29, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Aug. 31, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Sept. 13, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Sept. 15, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Sept. 22, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Sept. 28, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 2)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Oct. 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 1, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Oct. 5, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Oct. 9, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from Bremerton, Washington, Oct. 13, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 14, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 18, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 20, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 22, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Oct. 26, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 30, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Oct. 31, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother (birthday card) from USS Casablanca, Nov. 5, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 7, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 12, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 15, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 19, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 23, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Nov. 30, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Dec. 2, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 4, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Dec. 9, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 12, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 18, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Dec. 20, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Dec. 24, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Dec. 26, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Dec. 29, 1944 (Box 3, Folder 3)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Jan. 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 3, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 7, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 13, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 20, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 29, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Jan. 31, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 7, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 10, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - father from USS Casablanca, Feb. 13, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 15, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 17, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Feb. 26, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 3, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 6, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 12, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Mar. 16, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Mar. 19, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - family from USS Casablanca, Mar. 20, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Mar. 26, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [photocopy] mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 29, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Mar. 30, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [photocopy] parents from USS Casablanca, April 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - father from USS Casablanca, April 4, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [photocopy] father from USS Casablanca, April 5, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 7, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [photocopy] mother from USS Casablanca, April 10, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - [photocopy] father from USS Casablanca, April 11, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 13, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 20, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - father from USS Casablanca, April 22, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 27, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - father from USS Casablanca, April 28, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, April 28, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 4)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 5, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - father from USS Casablanca, May 6, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 10, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - father from USS Casablanca, May 14, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, May 14, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, May 21, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, June 6, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, June 11, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from Bremerton, Washington, July 4, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - father from USS Casablanca, July 18, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, July 18, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - father from USS Casablanca, July 30, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 2, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 4, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 8, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 15, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 16, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - mother from USS Casablanca, Aug. 20, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Aug. 28, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Sept. 1, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Sept. 12, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Sept. 13, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from USS Casablanca, Sept. 14, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from Oakland, California, Sept. 22, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from Oakland, California, Sept. 25, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from Oakland, California, Sept. 27, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 5)
    - parents from Taos, N. M., May 13, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Taos, N. M., May 30, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - mother from Taos, N. M., June 2, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      defends and explains his writing, etc.
    - mother from Taos, New Mexico, June 10, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - mother from Taos, New Mexico, June 18, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Taos, New Mexico, June 30, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Taos, New Mexico, July 8, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - family from Taos, New Mexico, July 24, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Taos, New Mexico, July 30, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - father from Taos, New Mexico, Aug. 14, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - mother from Taos, New Mexico, Aug. 19, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - mother from Taos, New Mexico, Aug. 30, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      1st mention of Stephen Spender
    - parents from San Francisco, Ca., Sept. 9, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Sept. 14, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Sept. 17, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Sept. 25, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Oct. 1, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      defends time in Taos, mentions Spender
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Oct. 16, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Oct. 22, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      comment on writer's methods and purpose
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Nov. 11, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Nov. 21, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
      repeats praise given him by Spender in lecture at Reed
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Nov. 26, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - mother from Portland, Oregon, Dec. 7, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Dec. 15, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - family from Portland, Oregon, Dec. 20, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Dec. 26, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 6)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Jan. 3, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Jan. 4, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Jan. 8, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Jan. 19, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Jan. 26, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Feb. 17, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Feb. 28, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, Mar. 7, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - father from Portland, Oregon, Mar. 16, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - mother from Portland, Oregon, April 9, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from Portland, Oregon, June 4, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - mother from Taos, N.M., Aug. 2, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      w/ANS from Dorothy to Mr. and Mrs. Goyen
    - parents from RMS Elizabeth, Sept. 24, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from RMS Elizabeth, Sept. 25, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Sept. 28, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from Paris, Oct. 1, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from Paris, Oct. 9, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Oct. 13, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Oct. 20, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Oct. 26, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - father from London, Nov. 2, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Nov. 7, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - Walt Berne to Mr. and Mrs. Goyen from London, Nov. 7, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
      describes Goyen's international reputation
    - parents from London, Nov. 18, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - parents from London book completed, Nov. 23, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from London, Dec. 5, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from Florence, Italy, Dec. 23, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
    - family from, Dec. 30, 1949 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Goyen to family, 1950-63; (233 items)
    - father from London, Jan. 8, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from London, Jan. 16, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from London, Jan. 29, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - family from St. Albans, Herts, Feb. 2, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Sister L. Brown to Goyen's parents from St. Albans, Feb. 10, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      regarding Goyen's knee surgery
    - parents from London, Feb. 16, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from London, Feb. 20, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - family from London, Mar. 1, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Mar. 17, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Mar. 26, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, April 7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Apr. 18, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Apr. 29, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, May 7, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, May 17, 1950 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - mother from New York, Feb. 3, 1952 (Folder Folder 2)
      w/ TLS to father Feb. 1, 1952
    - parents from New York, May 30, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, June 25, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - mother from New York, July 15, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from Shelter Island, New York, July 23, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - mother from East Hampton, Long Island, NY, Aug. 31, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 12, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
      w/ clippings from NY Times on Giant
    - mother from New York, Oct. 20, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from New York, Nov. 16, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - Joe Glasco to Mr. C.P. Goyen from Taos, NM, Nov. 24, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from Taos, NM, Dec. 7, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - parents from Taos, NM, Dec. 15, 1952 (Box 4, Folder 1)
    - mother from Taos, NM, Jan. 23, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from Taos, NM, Feb. 27, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from New York, Mar. 29, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Apr. 29, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, May 26, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - father from El Prado, NM, June 8, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, June 14, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - father from El Prado, NM, June 26, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, July 21, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Aug. 7, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - father from El Prado, NM, Aug. 16, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, Sept. 16, 1953
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Oct. 7, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Oct. 30, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, Nov. 8, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Nov. 20, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, Dec. 2, 1953 (Box 4, Folder 3)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, Jan. 11, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - mother from El Prado, NM, Feb. 13, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Telegram to parents from El Prado, NM, Feb. 22, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - L.B. Duffy, DVM, to Joe Glasco from Santa Fe, Mar. 3, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - D.E. Brett to Goyen's mother from Taos, NM, Mar. 27, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Sept. 17, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Oct. 6, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Oct. 22, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Oct. 30, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Telegram from Harry L. Richardson to Mrs. Goyen from Crockett, TX, Nov. 1, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Nov. 15, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Nov. 18, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from New York, NY, Nov. 28, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - Telegram to parents from New York, NY, Dec. 4, 1954 (Box 4, Folder 4)
    - parents from New York, Jan. 30, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Feb. 15, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - mother from New York, Mar. 10, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Apr. 3, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - Telegram to parents from New York, Apr. 10, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Apr. 20, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Apr. 27, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - mother from New York, May 5, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - father from New York, May 14, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - mother from New York, May 17, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, May 19, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, June 1, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, July 24, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Aug. 2, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Aug. 7, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - mother from New York, Aug. 17, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - father from New York, Aug. 17, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Aug. 21, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Sept. 12, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Sept. 18, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 4, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 16, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 24, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - mother from New York, Nov. __, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Nov. 3, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Nov. 17, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Nov. 25, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Dec. 10, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Dec. 22, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, Dec. 30, 1955 (Box 4, Folder 5)
    - parents from New York, NY, Jan. 19, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Feb. 7, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Feb. 12, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Feb. 22, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Mar. 11, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Mar. 26, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Apr. 8, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Apr. 14, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, NY, Apr. 29, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, June 10, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, July 6, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, July 20, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Aug. 16, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - father from El Prado, NM, Aug. 22, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from El Prado, NM, Sept. 3, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Sept. 23, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 14, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Oct. 21, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - mother from New York, Nov. __, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Nov. 11, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - father from New York, Nov. 26, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Dec. 2, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)
    - parents from New York, Dec. 11, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 6)